<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PX4 Drone Examples on VSPELLS HOMEPAGE</title><link>http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/</link><description>Recent content in PX4 Drone Examples on VSPELLS HOMEPAGE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 01:05:47 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Academia</title><link>http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/page2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 04:35:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/page2/</guid><description>Research DSLs Importance Powerful DSLs can be constructed for the operation of the robotic system. Hardware DSLs can also be created that monitor different subsystems such as battery depletion. The state space of the system can be thoroughly searched and verified. Heisenbugs that only show up in rare instances over long periods of time, can be uncovered using the P model checker. Not only can systems be modeled and tested, but the code for running the system can be auto generated from the models.</description></item><item><title>Real World Application</title><link>http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/page1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 04:35:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://evan-m7.github.io/vspells/posts3/page1/</guid><description>Overview P is a state machine based programming language for modeling and specifying complex distributed systems. P allows programmers to model their system as a collection of communicating state machines. P supports several backend analysis engines such as model checking and symbolic execution. P can be systematically tested and compiled into executable code. Combining P with MavSDK, which is a collection of libraries to interface with the MAVLink drone messaging framework, creates a powerful simulation and testing environment for drone robotics systems.</description></item></channel></rss>